Amr Moataz Elnaggar

Full-Stack Developer

Full-Stack Developer with two years of experience. posses wide skill set of technical and design skills including (.Net, WPF, Laravel, Angular, HTML/CSS, SQL) and (OOP, MVC, MVVM, UMLs, ERDs). Looking to secure a challenging role to bring knowledge in the field and develop new skills.



amrmoatazfcis@gmail.com 🔀

01152708018

Cairo, Egypt ♀

04 September, 1996 🎬

amr-moataz.itch.io/

linkedin.com/in/amr-elnaggar-990618112 in

github.com/AmrMoataz 🔘

EDUCATION

Computer Science Ain Shams University

10/2015 - 06/2019

WORK EXPERIENCE

Freelance Software developer Remotely

12/2020 - Present Back-End Developer Achievements/Tasks

• Work as a back-end developer for multiple different projects.

- Implement Restfull APIs for different projects and needs including (CRUD operations, OTP, User Registration and Authentication, database Manipulation, and push notification using FCM).
- Using different tools and framworks including (.Net, Laravel and Angular for some front-end functionalities).

Contact: Eng.Mohab Magdy - +201024741963

Full-Stack Developer Building Technology labs (BTL)

07/2019 - 12/2020

Cairo, Egypt

Full-stack Developer designing and implementing Web and Desktop Apps Achievements/Tasks

- Design and Implement new functionalities for Autodesk revit API using (revit API, C# WPF, SQL).
- Design and Implement desktop systems for the company's daily operations using (C#, WPF, SQL).
- Design and Implement Management system Web application for the company's (attendance, vacations, and tasks) using (.Net ASP, HTML/CSS, JQuery, Javascript, AJAX).
- Suggested and took responsability to transition from using (native javascript, JQuery, AJAX) for front-end towards using Angular 8 due to application needs.

Contact: Hend Mohammend -

https://www.linkedin.com/in/hend-mohamed-79a7151b8/

SKILLS

C#/Asp.Net MVC

Microsoft SQL server

C/C++ `

ADO.Net

Angular

HTML/CSS

LinQ

UMLs

GIT JOU

JQuery/AJAX

Laravel

openGL

HTML/CSS

IIS

PERSONAL PROJECTS

Augmented Reality FPS mobile game (01/2019 - 01/2020) ♂

- An Augmented Reality game that helps players to use their phones and search for other players to compete against each other.
- Used Object Detection (YOLOv3) algorithm for detecting object in the scene and adding it to game world.
- Used Unet multiplayer API in Unity3d for multiplayer functionalities.

Image Encryption and Compression (11/2018 - 12/2018)

- Implemented Algorithm for Encryption and Decryption and Image.
- Techniques used: Linear Feedback shift register.
- Implemented Algorithm for Image Compression.
- Techniques used: Huffman Tree.

ORGANIZATIONS

Open Source Community (07/2018 - 07/2019)
Senior Vice President

Open Source Community (07/2017 - 07/2018)

Public Relation Vice Head

Open Source Community (02/2017 - 07/2017)
Public Relation Member

LANGUAGES

Arabic

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

English

Native or Bilingual Proficiency